Guide to the Investigation Files of the Rapp-Coudert Committee TAM.533
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Microfilm Reel List (with Cross-Reference to Original Box and Folder Locations), 1919-1953
  - "U" Letters: Correspondence with the Committee - Includes United Parents Association "Report of SubCommittee of Legislative Committee on Rapp-Coudert Investigation, 1940-1941 (Reel R-7860, Reel frame 57-0125, Box-folder 21-RC610)
  - "W" Letters: Correspondence with the Committee - Includes Cost and Expenditure Report from City College Chemistry Department, 1927-1943 (Reel R-7860, Reel frame 57-0159, Box-folder 21-RC611)
  - Waivers of Immunity, Feb 1941-Nov 1941 (Reel R-7860, Reel frame 57-0315, Box-folder 21-RC612)
  - "X", "Y", "Z" Letters: Correspondence with the Committee, 1941-1943 (Reel R-7860, Reel frame 57-0432, Box-folder 21-RC613)
  - Various Throwaways, Leaflets: Includes Anti-War, Anti-Committee, General Strike, and Club Flyers as well as Teachers Union Memos and Bulletins and Election Platform of the Communist Party 1940, 1938-1940 (Reel R-7860, Reel frame 57-0455, Box-folder 21-RC614)